[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Gaylord M. Fockers unusual profession in the 2000 comedy Meet the Parents?", "correct_answer": "Nurse", "incorrect_answers": ["Pet mortician", "Kindergarten teacher", "Beautician"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which French Mediterranean island is the birthplace of Napol\u00e9on Bonaparte?", "correct_answer": "Corsica", "incorrect_answers": ["Cyprus", "Gozo", "Montecristo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character is related to the victim murdered in the beginning of the film The Da Vinci Code?", "correct_answer": "The victim was not related to anyone.", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Langdon", "Sir Leigh Teabing", "Sophie Neveu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which California community was the first of the Zodiac murders committed according to the 2007 movie of the same name?", "correct_answer": "Vallejo", "incorrect_answers": ["Long Beach", "Southgate", "Walnut Groves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Next Friday, Craig Jones compares someone to Left Eye from TLC.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actions has remained in history as the first official act of President Abraham Lincolns new administration?", "correct_answer": "Hiring a secretary named Nicolay", "incorrect_answers": ["Hiring a secretary named Kennedy", "Giving Winfield Scott command of the US Army", "Abolishing slavery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Eggplant, also known as aubergine, is a close relative of this other plant.", "correct_answer": "Tobacco", "incorrect_answers": ["Belladonna", "Hemlock", "Foxglove"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the first spacecraft to study the planet Uranus?", "correct_answer": "Voyager 2", "incorrect_answers": ["Pioneer 11", "Pioneer 10", "Voyager 1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A chromosome is a very long piece of Deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA) which contains genes. Which term refers to the number of chromosomes per cell in a species?", "correct_answer": "euploid number", "incorrect_answers": ["monoploid number", "haploid number", "aneuploid number"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is another name for Ursa Major?", "correct_answer": "The Great Bear", "incorrect_answers": ["The Great Tiger", "The Great Lion", "The Great Boar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year and season did the boys lives change forever in the movie Sleepers?", "correct_answer": "Summer 1967", "incorrect_answers": ["Fall 1968", "Summer 1968", "Fall 1967"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Travoltas mother appeared in the movie Grease.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]